<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on MIDAC Corporation</title>
    <link>https://www.midac.org/products/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on MIDAC Corporation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.midac.org/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vacuum Instruments</title>
      <link>https://www.midac.org/products/vacuum-instruments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.midac.org/products/vacuum-instruments/</guid>
      <description>Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TPC</title>
      <link>https://www.midac.org/products/tpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.midac.org/products/tpc/</guid>
      <description>Steady as a rock, day in and day out!
Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I1800</title>
      <link>https://www.midac.org/products/i1800/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.midac.org/products/i1800/</guid>
      <description>The I1800 line of FTIR spectrometers is the go-to for reliable on-line process monitoring. A rugged aluminum chassis houses the electronics, detector and interferometer module, and can be paired to any of the meter-length gas cells to ensure 24/7 process gas monitoring, preventing contamination issues and keeping your production running as it should be.
Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M4400</title>
      <link>https://www.midac.org/products/m4400/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.midac.org/products/m4400/</guid>
      <description>The M4400 line of cast-aluminum emissions spectrometers are able to perform fenceline monitoring, pollution controls and other real-world applications in all weather conditions. The fully-sealed unit can be combined with a source array for fencline monitoring or use the process heat directly as a source. For reliable environmental controls in real-world conditions, look no further than the M4400 series.
Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M4600</title>
      <link>https://www.midac.org/products/m4600/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.midac.org/products/m4600/</guid>
      <description>The M4600 line of sheet metal emissions spectrometers go the extra mile. A compact, lightweight chassis features a 3&amp;quot; integrated telescope, which offers a lightweight, portable unit perfect for field applications in volcanology, and non-permanent in-situ testing. This unit can be combined with a source array for fencline monitoring or use the process heat directly as a source. For in-field multi-gas measurement down to the PPM or PPB range, high-resolution and reliability, the M4600 is the one!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
